hey everybody who is coming it is a house
glittering practical video
you can use this video the practical
listening in camps ranch and is icepeak
you when i say they congo in the talk
about us resolution what is a new year's
resolution
this is a goal or in the checked that you
him for the next year when it's the end
of the here
some people make use resolution
demontage have good year in the meeting
let's talk about some common resolution
wine common use resolution is the lose
weight
many people plant lose weight by in
the now here this is a cork resolution
i can help you i hope i something na
easy to lose weight do it can be
difficult
juni to help foot and juni to exercise
many people go to the [ __ ] in January
because their new year's resolution is
the bus week na everyone straws work of
many people could ok and never common
use resolution is the study english more
this is a shitty new use resolution some
people want to learn english to help
create air
you speak english you can hem further
opportunities for some johns limits
stimulus and especially er johns juni 3 the
wright in english english as important
for many james may be english to help
your carrier to this here michael is
like the study more languages
oh yeah and never come and new year's
resolution yesterday
more pics some people are very
busy sophie dark face
other people or not go there be thing that did
want to improve and some people do
like drove
that a meteorite many people have used
resolution to read more
i think god of war to read more to a
widely read many books to see how many
books to you want to be with you maybe
you can read books in english so here
30 euro resolution okay and  nether commonly
used resolution
is to learn and new activity this is
a photo of the arm and yes two babies
that you ready
some people learn to your sport other
people learn and skill
eager to learn new things maybe you
license plate class too long and thumping you
were many places that teach you define
skills you can look for class seigneur
city and never common use resolution is
the quit smoking
this is to van resolution political
iTunes mug
so iphone not too mercury aykut step other
bad habits
free sample high tea to let super
so maybe  aischylos superbaziel
or maybe a city norwich de pols die
zargar resolution
by minitip by use resolution
I think this is [ __ ] the people want to
accomplish goals something cultuurcampus
kools
also no wetzel for today leave a
comment
intel more view high resolution for this
here if he stares your neck
[Music]
[Applause]